ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 78)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 79)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 80)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 81)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 82)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 83)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 84)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 85)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 86)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 87)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 88)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 89)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 90)
- Finance-Appeals and acknowledgements, 1940-1951 (Box 43, Folder 91)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Finance reports and acknowledgements, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Appeals, general correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Appeals, general correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Appeals, general correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Appeals, general correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  Partial list of foundations includes: American Association for Adult Education, American Jewish Committee, American Peoples' Fund, Brandeis Foundation, Carnegie Corporation, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, CIO-Political Action Committee, Ford Foundation, General Education Board, Greater New York Fund, Goodwill Fund, Lucius Littauer Foundation, Marshall Foundation, Marshall Civil Liberties Trust Fund, National CIO War Relief, A.Philip Randolph Foundation, Rockefeller Foundation, Julius Rosenwald Foundation, Sarah S. Ollesheimer Fund, Phelps Stokes Fund, Florence Simms Memorial Scholarship Fund, William Roy Smith Fund, Special Services Committee, John Hay Whitney Foundation, U.S. Dept. of Labor, U.S. Dept. of State, U.S. Economic Cooperative Administration
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 49)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 50)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 51)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 52)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 53)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 54)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 55)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 56)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 57)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 58)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 60)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 61)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 62)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 63)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 64)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 65)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 66)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 67)
- Appeals to individual foundations including Colt's correspondence, financial and other ALES reports, and budgets, 1934-1951 (Box 44, Folder 68)
- ALES Director's Field Reports, 1934-1951 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  filed according to area include reports of recruitment of students in various cities, unions, YWCAs, churches, and other social action agencies
- ALES Director's Field Reports, 1934-1951 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- ALES Director's Field Reports, 1934-1951 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Programs and reports on minority projects in St. Louis and New Jersey (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Midwest conference proceedings, 1934-1951 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Sample annual reports (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Scrapbooks, 1952-1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  containing photographs, clippings, publicity and reprints illustrating ALES programs and conferences
- Scrapbooks, 1952-1962 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Scrapbooks, 1952-1962 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  notes and incomplete sets of minutes, ballots, and agendas
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Board, Executive Committee, 1950-1961 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- ALES chronological developments (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 39)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 42)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Committees (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Union Education Directors Advisory Group, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 50)
  includes assessments by Dr. Lindeman, Dr. F. E. Johnson, and Hew Roberts as well as participants
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 53)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 54)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 55)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 56)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 57)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 58)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 59)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 60)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 61)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 62)
- Appraisal and evaluation of ALES conferences and events (Box 47, Folder 63)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Closing conference, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Archives committee, correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  re arrangement and transfer of records to New York State School of Industrial Labor Relations
- Archives committee, correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Archives committee, correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  correspondents include Hilda Smith, Amy Hewes, Gladys Palmer, and Mildred Woodbury
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Archives committee, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Coit, biographical data (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Analyses and studies of local communities to assist in program planning (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Analyses and studies of local communities to assist in program planning (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Brownie Lee Jones' study in japan (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Study of community resources (Box 48, Folder 27)
  Louisiana, Missouri, Ohio, Tennessee, Texas, Arizona, and New Mexico as basis for selection of program sites
- Needs in labor education, proposal, reports, conference, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Annual reports, 1957-1961 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Annual reports, 1952-1956 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Project and field reports, staff memos, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  include the following staff: Marie E. Algor, Edward J, Chesky, Chester Graham, Rosalind Harris, David Heaps, Brownie Lee Jones, Chris Jorgenson, Louise L. McLaren, Orlie Pell, and Astrad Raah
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Individual staff field reports, letters exploring new areas, statistical sheets, and reports of U. N. schools and CIO summer schools, 1952- 1962 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Staff memos and meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Reports and other mss (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 58)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 59)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 60)
- Field reports, 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 61)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  include number of participants in School on World Affairs, conferences, and names of participating international and local unions
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Statistics on major ALES activities, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Box file describing international and local union support (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Box file of conference participants arranged by name of union (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Personnel and job applications, 1952-1959 (Box 52, Folder 1)